flvmplayer.com 2014-04-28

# FLV MPlayer | Terms & Conditions

## 1\. Product description

This product is a media player which supports FLV, F4V, MP4 and MOV video formats. It plays videos in HD and Full Screen. You can create your own personal playlists. It is an easy-to-use and intuitive application.

## 2\. Responsibilities

The Society does not give any guarantees nor it is responsible for third-party programs the user downloads, including third-party toolbars. It is duty of the user to previously decide whether the download and install of the program or toolbar is suitable or not, and the con-formity with the license conditions the user may have to agree with.

## 3\. Privacy Policy

This clause contains the Privacy Policy, which regulates important issues about the users' privacy of this website.

### 3.1 Data Collection

The Society will collect and treat any data the users insert in the available forms of this website or by any other means linked to the Society, as well as any other information the Society may automatically capture in relation with the technical specifications of the user's equipment: operating system version, internet browser version, CPU type, internet connec-tion type, operating system language, IP address, cookies activation, Java activation and screen resolution. All of these will now be referred to as 'Data'.

Data can be personal, as defined in the current Spanish legislation, and facilitating it in the forms, or in the case of automatically-captured data, browsing through the website, the user implicitly agrees to the data collection, archive indexation and to be treated according to the present Privacy Policy.

The user agrees not to provide personal information regarding third-parties, even with their agreement, and will assume full responsibility of its actions.

### 3.2. Purpose of processing

The society will process the data in order to manage the correct maintenance, develop-ment and control of this web site and the services offered; in particular, to respond the incidents reported by the users in relation to the services offered in this web site.

Also, when authorized by the user, the Society may use your data to send you commercial communications, including by electronic means, to promote goods and services of the company or other third parties. The authorization provided by the user may be revoked by him at any time.

The user specifically authorizes that, for any of the purposes expressed above, the Society can, personally or through charge treatment, deal data outside the European Union, in particular in Peru and Uruguay, even if the legislation of the country in which they are trea-ted does not provide personal data a level of protection comparable to Spanish legislation.

The data will not be used for purposes other than those specified in this privacy policy, or disclosed to third parties, without the user's consent.

### 3.3. Use of cookies

This web site uses cookies so that the Society can provide a better service to the user. The user can configure their Internet browser so that it notifies him/her of the receipt of cookies, giving the user the chance to decide whether to accept them or not.

### 3.4. Access rights, rectification, cancellation and opposition

The user can exercise the access rights, rectification, cancellation and opposition recogni-zed by the Spanish law on protection of personal data in relation to the Data. To do this, the user may contact Society by sending a message to support@bechiroapps.com or through any other service of customer that the society may have established at that time.

### 3.5. Other web sites

This privacy policy is only applicable to this web site. The Society does not warrant nor takes responsibility for privacy policies applied on websites linked from this website or the processing of data that can make those responsible.

## 4\. General

The company may revise and modify the terms of service at any time by updating this page. The conditions applied to the Service contracted by the user will be those published at the time of recruitment.

These conditions are governed by Spanish legislation. The user may not cease of this made agreement, every time that the service will be provided immediately after their en-gagement with the user's consent.

The agreement will be formalized in the language selected by the user from the availables on the web site. There may be copies of these conditions of service in several languages; user can perform its request via the support form.

The contents of this web site are protected by rights of intellectual or industrial property of the company and/or third parties. The user will not delete, alter, elude or manipulate pro-tection devices or any security system that can be installed on this web site.

## 5\. Instructions to uninstall the software from this web:

  1. Go to (Start)-> (Computer)
  2. Uninstall or change a program
  3. Select FLV Media Player version 1.3
  4. Click on Remove (Uninstall)
  5. Click 'Yes' to confirm the Uninstall
  6. And finally, when the installation is done, we can see a message saying that the uninstall process was satisfactory. Click on 'OK'

## 6\. Society's identification and contact information

If the user wishes to make any inquiry or complaint, he/she can put in contact with the So-ciety through the support form available on the web site or by sending a message to the e-mail address: support@bechiroapps.com

Bechiro S.L. is a Spanish company located in Barcelona, Medes 4-6 Local. Registered in the mercantile registry of Barcelona, with CIF: B65654329.
